<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--
 This is a WordPress eXtended RSS file generated by WordPress as an export of your site.
 It contains information about your site's posts, pages, comments, categories, and other content.
 You may use this file to transfer that content from one site to another.
 This file is not intended to serve as a complete backup of your site.

 To import this information into a WordPress site follow these steps:
 1. Log in to that site as an administrator.
 2. Go to Tools: Import in the WordPress admin panel.
 3. Install the "WordPress" importer from the list.
 4. Activate & Run Importer.
 5. Upload this file using the form provided on that page.
 6. You will first be asked to map the authors in this export file to users
    on the site. For each author, you may choose to map to an
    existing user on the site or to create a new user.
 7. WordPress will then import each of the posts, pages, comments, categories, etc.
    contained in this file into your site.
-->
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:excerpt="http://wordpress.org/export/1.2/excerpt/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:wp="http://wordpress.org/export/1.2/">
  <channel>
<title>Customer Service</title>
<link>http://hzhapr15a.dmclub.net/cutomerservices</link>
<description>Just another Bizclub site</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 08 May 2015 17:09:07 +0000</pubDate>
<language>en-GB</language>
<wp:wxr_version>1.2</wp:wxr_version>
<wp:base_site_url>http://hzhapr15a.dmclub.net/</wp:base_site_url>
<wp:base_blog_url>http://hzhapr15a.dmclub.net/cutomerservices</wp:base_blog_url>
<wp:wp_author>
  <wp:author_login>admin</wp:author_login>
  <wp:author_email>jc@startupnow.co.uk</wp:author_email>
  <wp:author_display_name><![CDATA[admin]]></wp:author_display_name>
  <wp:author_first_name><![CDATA[]]></wp:author_first_name>
  <wp:author_last_name><![CDATA[]]></wp:author_last_name>
</wp:wp_author>
<wp:wp_author>
  <wp:author_login>rwhite</wp:author_login>
  <wp:author_email>rwhite@pro-excellence.com</wp:author_email>
  <wp:author_display_name><![CDATA[Richard White]]></wp:author_display_name>
  <wp:author_first_name><![CDATA[]]></wp:author_first_name>
  <wp:author_last_name><![CDATA[]]></wp:author_last_name>
</wp:wp_author>
<wp:category>
  <wp:term_id>2</wp:term_id>
  <wp:category_nicename>customer-complaints</wp:category_nicename>
  <wp:category_parent/>
  <wp:cat_name><![CDATA[Customer Complaints]]></wp:cat_name>
</wp:category>
<wp:category>
  <wp:term_id>3</wp:term_id>
  <wp:category_nicename>customer-feedback</wp:category_nicename>
  <wp:category_parent/>
  <wp:cat_name><![CDATA[Customer Feedback]]></wp:cat_name>
</wp:category>
<wp:category>
  <wp:term_id>4</wp:term_id>
  <wp:category_nicename>customer-relationships</wp:category_nicename>
  <wp:category_parent/>
  <wp:cat_name><![CDATA[Customer Relationships]]></wp:cat_name>
</wp:category>
<wp:category>
  <wp:term_id>1</wp:term_id>
  <wp:category_nicename>uncategorised</wp:category_nicename>
  <wp:category_parent/>
  <wp:cat_name><![CDATA[Uncategorised]]></wp:cat_name>
</wp:category>

<item>
  <title>Dog-Smile-2</title>
  <link>http://hzhapr15a.dmclub.net/cutomerservices/?attachment_id=9</link>
  <pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2015 10:48:22 +0000</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>admin</dc:creator>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">http://hzhapr15a.dmclub.net/cutomerservices/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2015/03/Dog-Smile-23.jpg</guid>
  <description/>
  <content:encoded><![CDATA[]]></content:encoded>
  <excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
  <wp:post_id>9</wp:post_id>
  <wp:post_date>2015-03-10 10:48:22</wp:post_date>
  <wp:post_date_gmt>2015-03-10 10:48:22</wp:post_date_gmt>
  <wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
  <wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
  <wp:post_name>dog-smile-2</wp:post_name>
  <wp:status>inherit</wp:status>
  <wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
  <wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
  <wp:post_type>attachment</wp:post_type>
  <wp:post_password/>
  <wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
  <wp:attachment_url>http://hzhapr15a.dmclub.net/cutomerservices/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2015/03/Dog-Smile-23.jpg</wp:attachment_url>
</item>
<item>
  <title>Caroline-Cooper</title>
  <link>http://hzhapr15a.dmclub.net/cutomerservices/do-your-customers-love-you/caroline-cooper/</link>
  <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2015 22:06:59 +0000</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>rwhite</dc:creator>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">http://hzhapr15a.dmclub.net/cutomerservices/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2015/03/Caroline-Cooper3.jpg</guid>
  <description/>
  <content:encoded><![CDATA[]]></content:encoded>
  <excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
  <wp:post_id>12</wp:post_id>
  <wp:post_date>2015-03-25 22:06:59</wp:post_date>
  <wp:post_date_gmt>2015-03-25 22:06:59</wp:post_date_gmt>
  <wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
  <wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
  <wp:post_name>caroline-cooper</wp:post_name>
  <wp:status>inherit</wp:status>
  <wp:post_parent>13</wp:post_parent>
  <wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
  <wp:post_type>attachment</wp:post_type>
  <wp:post_password/>
  <wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
  <wp:attachment_url>http://hzhapr15a.dmclub.net/cutomerservices/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2015/03/Caroline-Cooper3.jpg</wp:attachment_url>
</item>
<item>
  <title>Article: Do your customers love you?</title>
  <link>http://hzhapr15a.dmclub.net/cutomerservices/do-your-customers-love-you/</link>
  <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2015 22:12:42 +0000</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>rwhite</dc:creator>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">http://hzhapr15a.dmclub.net/cutomerservices/?p=13</guid>
  <description/>
  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<a href="http://hzhapr15a.dmclub.net/cutomerservices/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2015/03/Caroline-Cooper3.jpg"><img class="alignright size-medium wp-image-12" src="http://hzhapr15a.dmclub.net/cutomerservices/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2015/03/Caroline-Cooper3-294x300.jpg" alt="Caroline-Cooper" /></a>Knowing what our customers think of us is great, but it can be hard to tell if our customers really love us or not.

Asking customers for feedback may seem a bit of a cliché, but is important nevertheless. The small fact we even bother asking for their feedback shows we care about them and what they think.

We may not always like what we hear, but beware the silent customer. Without the chance to feed back an unhappy customer is most likely to vote with their feet, and simply stop buying from us. With the amount of time and effort that goes into getting a customer, this is a tragic waste.

Worse still they tell others. These days that’s not just friends and family… but every Twitter follower, Facebook friend and review site you can name.

The best time to get this feedback is either before they’ve concluded their business with us, or <strong>immediately </strong>afterwards. Why?
<h3>Getting direct feedback there and then means:</h3>
<ul>
	<li>We get the opportunity to resolve any issues before it’s too late. We get a chance to turn things around and leave the customer happy. Surprisingly, a customer who’s had a problem resolved well will often be more loyal than when everything has gone just as expected. It makes it more noteworthy.</li>
	<li>We can be made aware of a problem before other customers are affected so we get the chance to put things right (and prevent an on-going spiral of unhappy customers).</li>
	<li>All the events are still fresh in ours and the customer’s mind, so it’s easier to make sense of it and nothing gets distorted or blown out of proportion.</li>
	<li>We have a chance to ask questions if need be, to really understand their feedback (something you can ever do with an impersonal questionnaire after the event). The more you listen and understand the issue, the easier it is to resolve and the happier the customer.</li>
	<li>If there’s anything they didn’t like the customer gets a chance to get it off their chest and reduce the likelihood of them sharing their dissatisfaction with the whole world.</li>
</ul>
But, with this being the month of love, don’t we want to know about the things they <strong>love</strong> about us too? Of course we do.
<h3>Getting <strong>positive feedback</strong> means:</h3>
<ul>
	<li>We get to understand what our customers like so we ensure we keep on doing it.</li>
	<li>We learn what’s important to them and why they choose to buy from us rather than our competitors, so we can make more of it. Maybe even use it as a point of differentiation.</li>
	<li>While they recount their positive comments it reinforces in their mind everything we got right.</li>
	<li>We can potentially use their feedback for testimonials or to elicit referrals.</li>
	<li>It’s a great morale boost for us and the team.</li>
</ul>
So, do <strong>you</strong> want to know if <strong>your</strong> customers love you?

Well, get out there and ask them!
<h2>About the author</h2>
Caroline Cooper is founder of <a href="http://www.naturallyloyal.com/">Naturally Loyal</a> who helps businesses to get more sales through their existing customers. Caroline specialises in working with independent businesses, helping them build loyalty through giving customers outstanding experiences and staying on their radar to trigger repeat business. She is author of Amazon bestseller the ‘Hotel Success Handbook’ and regular columnist for a number of business journals and periodicals, including ‘Customer Experience Magazine’ and Surrey Chamber of Commerce’s magazine ‘The Chamber’.]]></content:encoded>
  <excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
  <wp:post_id>13</wp:post_id>
  <wp:post_date>2015-03-25 22:12:42</wp:post_date>
  <wp:post_date_gmt>2015-03-25 22:12:42</wp:post_date_gmt>
  <wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
  <wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
  <wp:post_name>do-your-customers-love-you</wp:post_name>
  <wp:status>publish</wp:status>
  <wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
  <wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
  <wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
  <wp:post_password/>
  <wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
  <category domain="category" nicename="customer-relationships"><![CDATA[Customer Relationships]]></category>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_bizclub_static_content</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_bizclub_static_title</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_bizclub_top_contributors</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_bizclub_related_pages</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[a:2:{s:3:"csv";s:0:"";s:4:"data";a:1:{i:0;s:0:"";}}]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_bizclub_sub_title</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_bizclub_wpt_settings</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
</item>
<item>
  <title>Article: The easy way to gain customer feedback</title>
  <link>http://hzhapr15a.dmclub.net/cutomerservices/the-easy-way-to-gain-customer-feedback/</link>
  <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2015 22:15:47 +0000</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>rwhite</dc:creator>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">http://hzhapr15a.dmclub.net/cutomerservices/?p=15</guid>
  <description/>
  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<a href="http://hzhapr15a.dmclub.net/cutomerservices/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2015/03/Caroline-Cooper3.jpg"><img class="alignright size-medium wp-image-12" src="http://hzhapr15a.dmclub.net/cutomerservices/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2015/03/Caroline-Cooper3-294x300.jpg" alt="Caroline-Cooper" /></a>In a previous article, I emphasised the importance of getting customer feedback if you want them to love you. In this article I am going to give you my 5 top tips for getting that all-important feedback.<!--more-->
<h3>1. Make giving feedback easy</h3>
In a bricks and mortar business, where customers visit your premises, you and your team need to visible and approachable. Everyone in the team should welcome, and know how to handle, feedback.

Give customers choice; not insisting on filling out a comments card or going to a web based form. Chances are customers won’t bother, and that nugget of information is lost forever.

Enable customers to speak to a real person. Have an easy-to-find (non-premium) phone number, which if it’s not manned 24/7, provides the facility to take a message on a promise to phone back.

Provide an email address as an alternative; an account which gets checked regularly, preferably one with a real name attached to it rather than an impersonal enquires@ or info@ address.
<h3>2. Ask the right questions</h3>
Using open questions (which require more than a one word answer), homes in on specifics. So instead of: ‘was everything OK?’ you might ask: ‘I know you were in two minds about the size, how was it?'

Give a reason for asking. So instead of: ‘did everything arrive OK?’ you might ask: ‘as we’ve just made some changes to our delivery process, we’d love to hear how you’d rate your delivery driver today’.

Ask for clarification if needed. So in the last example, if the customer replies: ‘not that impressed’, follow up to find out what the driver did that didn’t impress them.

Encourage customers to feed back via social media by promoting your @twitter address and Facebook page, along with any other social media or review sites relevant to your industry.
<h3> 3. Keep your ears and eyes open</h3>
If you want to know what customers REALLY think, look out for non-verbal cues that everything is as it should be. For example, spotting a change in behaviour: the client isn’t returning calls; the customer stops ordering a specific product; there’s hesitation in their voice when asked a question.

Keep monitoring social media so you can listen to what customers are sharing amongst themselves. And then respond in the moment. What better way to answer a customer query or appease a disgruntled customer than picking up on their post, thanking them for their feedback and responding straight away when they’re least expecting it?

Ensure you have set up Google Alerts so you know when you’re being talked about elsewhere too.
<h3>4. Use 3rd party help when needed</h3>
Another way to gather the ‘warts and all’ feedback is to enlist the help of a third party. I know from personal experience of running workshops for the past 25+ years that people are scared of offending you. So they’ll answer with what they think you <strong>want</strong> to hear. Unfortunately that’s not always that helpful!

So whereas feedback there and then is great for resolving issues as they arrive and to stop them festering, it may not pick up on all aspects that need attention or could be capitalised on. That’s where outsourcing may help.

Whether via a questionnaire or phone calls, it’s what’s best fit with the culture and nature of the business (not necessarily your industry – I’m all for breaking away from how your competitors might do things to be bold and be different!)
<h3>5. Acknowledge and act on the feedback</h3>
According to a recent survey by Maritz Research, 51% of people who make a complaint online expect a response, but 85% of those questioned have never received one!

Businesses who want to make best use of feedback acknowledge and thank customers who provide it - however good, bad or indifferent it is. It’s not only good manners, it shows a caring attitude.

Failing to acknowledge feedback means your customers won’t bother telling you next time when there’s something you really DO need to know about.

Of course, once you have all this valuable feedback you need to act upon it, and tell your customers what you’re doing too.

A business who fails to act on feedback and report back to the customer what they are doing about it is wasting a golden opportunity to build trust and create that all-important customer loyalty.
<h2>About the author</h2>
Caroline Cooper is founder of <a href="http://www.naturallyloyal.com/">Naturally Loyal</a> who helps businesses to get more sales through their existing customers. Caroline specialises in working with independent businesses, helping them build loyalty through giving customers outstanding experiences and staying on their radar to trigger repeat business. She is author of Amazon bestseller the ‘Hotel Success Handbook’ and regular columnist for a number of business journals and periodicals, including ‘Customer Experience Magazine’ and Surrey Chamber of Commerce’s magazine ‘The Chamber’.]]></content:encoded>
  <excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
  <wp:post_id>15</wp:post_id>
  <wp:post_date>2015-03-25 22:15:47</wp:post_date>
  <wp:post_date_gmt>2015-03-25 22:15:47</wp:post_date_gmt>
  <wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
  <wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
  <wp:post_name>the-easy-way-to-gain-customer-feedback</wp:post_name>
  <wp:status>publish</wp:status>
  <wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
  <wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
  <wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
  <wp:post_password/>
  <wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
  <category domain="category" nicename="customer-feedback"><![CDATA[Customer Feedback]]></category>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_bizclub_static_content</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_bizclub_static_title</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_bizclub_top_contributors</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_bizclub_related_pages</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[a:2:{s:3:"csv";s:0:"";s:4:"data";a:1:{i:0;s:0:"";}}]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_bizclub_sub_title</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_bizclub_wpt_settings</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
</item>
<item>
  <title>Article: Why customer complaints can be good for business</title>
  <link>http://hzhapr15a.dmclub.net/cutomerservices/why-customer-complaints-can-be-good-for-business/</link>
  <pubDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2015 16:42:38 +0000</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>rwhite</dc:creator>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">http://hzhapr15a.dmclub.net/cutomerservices/?p=19</guid>
  <description/>
  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<a href="http://hzhapr15a.dmclub.net/cutomerservices/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2015/03/Caroline-Cooper3.jpg"><img class="alignright size-medium wp-image-12" src="http://hzhapr15a.dmclub.net/cutomerservices/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2015/03/Caroline-Cooper3-294x300.jpg" alt="Caroline-Cooper" /></a>It seems counter intuitive, but as a business we should welcome complaints! WHY?

Because the alternative is we’re left not knowing when the customer isn’t happy.

Obviously prevention is better than cure. So keep customers informed if you foresee an issue, before it becomes a problem.

But of course you're not always able to pre-empt problems and won’t be able to avoid all complaints. Accidents happen, things get missed or events occur that are totally out of our control. So what can you do to lessen the impact on your customers’ experience and limit the potential damage to your customer relationships and your reputation?

Aim to spot problems as early as possible. Listen and observe. You can often sense there’s an issue long before you get told directly.

It can be easy to get defensive when you receive feedback, particularly when you feel it is not justified or you totally disagree with it.

But something must have triggered their perception.  So listen to what your customer is saying.

Here are 4 key stages to handling a complaint effectively irrespective of the cause:
<ul>
	<li>Listen</li>
	<li>Show empathy</li>
	<li>Agree on an acceptable solution</li>
	<li>Action</li>
</ul>
Let’s look at each stage in more detail
<h3>Listen</h3>
Listen without interrupting to allow the customer to get it off their chest. Whilst listening think about your reaction; your body language, facial expressions or tone might all give negative messages back to the customer.

Getting irritated or angry you will only make the situation worse. It may be the 100<sup>th</sup> time you’ve heard this complaint, but your customer does not know this, so be patient as you listen. Stay calm, maintain eye contact and listen. Ask more questions if you need to in order to clarify. Focus on facts, but look to understand how they feel too.

It is useful to reflect back to the customer your understanding of the issue. Summarising their points using their words can show you’ve understood correctly, and it reassures the customer you have all the facts.

Maybe the problem was caused by the customer, but never accuse. This only makes the problem worse. No; the customer isn’t always right, but your goal should be to leave the customer positive and wanting to do business with you again; not to embarrass them, teach them a lesson or score points.
<h3>Show empathy</h3>
Acknowledge and show you understand how the customer feels and show your concern, even if it’s not your fault.

The least you can do is to apologise (even if you're just apologising that they feel that way).

Try to look at the situation from their perspective:
<ul>
	<li>they might be frustrated because they’ve already spent more time than they’d allocated getting to this point</li>
	<li>they may be disappointed as you’re not able to deliver what they had in mind</li>
	<li>they might be angry they’ve invested a lot of money on something that has not yet lived up to their expectation</li>
	<li>they might be embarrassed because they didn’t fully understand everything that was involved and now realise there’s a whole lot more on their shoulders</li>
	<li>they might be feeling anxious as they’d made a commitment to one of their own customers that they now can’t fulfil</li>
</ul>
Put yourself in their shoes and imagine how you might feel in their situation. Your tone of voice is very important when responding. If you are overly calm you may come across as not being concerned or even patronising.

If you are in the wrong, be bold, and own up. Your customers will thank you for being honest and this all helps to keep the trust.

The very last thing to do is make excuses. Frankly your customers don’t care about your staff shortages, that your suppliers have let you down, that the ‘x’ machine is broken, your company policy, or that no one else has complained. Nor are they interested in hearing “that’s nothing to do with us; it’s down to the organisers / council / landlord….etc.”

Irrespective of whose fault it is your aim should always be to do what you can to have the customer go away happy.
<h3>Agree an acceptable solution</h3>
Getting it off their chest might be all a customer wants and a simple apology is all that’s needed.

But others will be seeking a resolution. So focus on looking for potential solutions.

It’s important to strike a balance between being positive but showing concern. Use positive language that demonstrates your desire to resolve it. Such as: “<em>Let’s see what we can sort out for you.”  “I’m sure we can get this sorted.”  “If I do ___ would that be acceptable?”</em>
<h3>Agree an acceptable solution</h3>
Of course, having agreed a resolution do what you say you’ll do.

Then follow up to reassure customers by showing how you are going to avoid the problem in future, so you can re-establish trust. A customer is unlikely to want to come back if they think they are going to encounter the same problem next time.

The way you handle the situation is what your customers will remember and if you can go above and beyond to resolve the problem, even when it’s down to a third party, customer error or even an act of God, it’s your resolve of the situation they’ll remember, not the cause.
<h2>About the author</h2>
Caroline Cooper is founder of <a href="http://www.naturallyloyal.com/">Naturally Loyal</a> who helps businesses to get more sales through their existing customers. Caroline specialises in working with independent businesses, helping them build loyalty through giving customers outstanding experiences and staying on their radar to trigger repeat business. She is author of Amazon bestseller the ‘Hotel Success Handbook’ and regular columnist for a number of business journals and periodicals, including ‘Customer Experience Magazine’ and Surrey Chamber of Commerce’s magazine ‘The Chamber’.]]></content:encoded>
  <excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
  <wp:post_id>19</wp:post_id>
  <wp:post_date>2015-03-31 17:42:38</wp:post_date>
  <wp:post_date_gmt>2015-03-31 16:42:38</wp:post_date_gmt>
  <wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
  <wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
  <wp:post_name>why-customer-complaints-can-be-good-for-business</wp:post_name>
  <wp:status>publish</wp:status>
  <wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
  <wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
  <wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
  <wp:post_password/>
  <wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
  <category domain="category" nicename="customer-complaints"><![CDATA[Customer Complaints]]></category>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_bizclub_static_content</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_bizclub_static_title</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_bizclub_top_contributors</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_bizclub_related_pages</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[a:2:{s:3:"csv";s:0:"";s:4:"data";a:1:{i:0;s:0:"";}}]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_bizclub_sub_title</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_bizclub_wpt_settings</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
</item>
<item>
  <title>Customer Service</title>
  <link>http://hzhapr15a.dmclub.net/cutomerservices/</link>
  <pubDate>Tue, 07 Apr 2015 11:33:57 +0000</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>rwhite</dc:creator>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">http://hzhapr15a.dmclub.net/cutomerservices/?page_id=26</guid>
  <description/>
  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<h4><a href="http://hzhapr15a.dmclub.net/cutomerservices/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2015/04/Customer-service-small3.jpg"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-30" src="http://hzhapr15a.dmclub.net/cutomerservices/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2015/04/Customer-service-small3.jpg" alt="Customer service small" /></a></h4>
<h4></h4>
<h4>Welcome to the Customer Service BizClub interest area. Our mission is to turn your customers into loyal ambassadors for your business.</h4>
<h4>Through a combination of articles, seminars, clinics, and masterclasses we will be covering the following subject areas:</h4>
<h2>Customer experience</h2>
The art and science of how to improve the way in which your customers interact with your staff.
<h2>Customer feedback</h2>
Providing you with ideas and expert advice on how to find out what your customers think, what they like, and what they want your business to do better
<h2>Staff engagement</h2>
How to get your staff onboard and engaged in the process of continually improving customer service levels.
<h2>Service culture</h2>
How to develop and sustain a culture of quality customer service that will keep your customers coming back time after time.
<h2>Systems and processes</h2>
How to ensure that each and every one of yours customers consistently get quality service they expect/]]></content:encoded>
  <excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
  <wp:post_id>26</wp:post_id>
  <wp:post_date>2015-04-07 12:33:57</wp:post_date>
  <wp:post_date_gmt>2015-04-07 11:33:57</wp:post_date_gmt>
  <wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
  <wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
  <wp:post_name>customer-service</wp:post_name>
  <wp:status>publish</wp:status>
  <wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
  <wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
  <wp:post_type>page</wp:post_type>
  <wp:post_password/>
  <wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_wp_page_template</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_bizclub_static_content</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_bizclub_static_title</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_bizclub_top_contributors</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_bizclub_related_pages</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[a:2:{s:3:"csv";s:0:"";s:4:"data";a:1:{i:0;s:0:"";}}]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_bizclub_sub_title</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_bizclub_wpt_settings</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[2,2,1,2,1,0,2,0,0,1,0]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_bizclub_page_type</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[wel]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
</item>
<item>
  <title>Customer service small</title>
  <link>http://hzhapr15a.dmclub.net/cutomerservices/customer-service/customer-service-small/</link>
  <pubDate>Tue, 07 Apr 2015 12:25:17 +0000</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>rwhite</dc:creator>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">http://hzhapr15a.dmclub.net/cutomerservices/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2015/04/Customer-service-small3.jpg</guid>
  <description/>
  <content:encoded><![CDATA[]]></content:encoded>
  <excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
  <wp:post_id>30</wp:post_id>
  <wp:post_date>2015-04-07 13:25:17</wp:post_date>
  <wp:post_date_gmt>2015-04-07 12:25:17</wp:post_date_gmt>
  <wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
  <wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
  <wp:post_name>customer-service-small</wp:post_name>
  <wp:status>inherit</wp:status>
  <wp:post_parent>26</wp:post_parent>
  <wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
  <wp:post_type>attachment</wp:post_type>
  <wp:post_password/>
  <wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
  <wp:attachment_url>http://hzhapr15a.dmclub.net/cutomerservices/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2015/04/Customer-service-small3.jpg</wp:attachment_url>
</item>
  </channel>
</rss>
