<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--
 This is a WordPress eXtended RSS file generated by WordPress as an export of your site.
 It contains information about your site's posts, pages, comments, categories, and other content.
 You may use this file to transfer that content from one site to another.
 This file is not intended to serve as a complete backup of your site.

 To import this information into a WordPress site follow these steps:
 1. Log in to that site as an administrator.
 2. Go to Tools: Import in the WordPress admin panel.
 3. Install the "WordPress" importer from the list.
 4. Activate & Run Importer.
 5. Upload this file using the form provided on that page.
 6. You will first be asked to map the authors in this export file to users
    on the site. For each author, you may choose to map to an
    existing user on the site or to create a new user.
 7. WordPress will then import each of the posts, pages, comments, categories, etc.
    contained in this file into your site.
-->
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:excerpt="http://wordpress.org/export/1.2/excerpt/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:wp="http://wordpress.org/export/1.2/">
  <channel>
<title>Finance</title>
<link>http://hzhapr15a.dmclub.net/finances</link>
<description>Just another Bizclub site</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 08 May 2015 17:09:08 +0000</pubDate>
<language>en-GB</language>
<wp:wxr_version>1.2</wp:wxr_version>
<wp:base_site_url>http://hzhapr15a.dmclub.net/</wp:base_site_url>
<wp:base_blog_url>http://hzhapr15a.dmclub.net/finances</wp:base_blog_url>
<wp:wp_author>
  <wp:author_login>rwhite</wp:author_login>
  <wp:author_email>rwhite@pro-excellence.com</wp:author_email>
  <wp:author_display_name><![CDATA[Richard White]]></wp:author_display_name>
  <wp:author_first_name><![CDATA[]]></wp:author_first_name>
  <wp:author_last_name><![CDATA[]]></wp:author_last_name>
</wp:wp_author>
<wp:category>
  <wp:term_id>2</wp:term_id>
  <wp:category_nicename>cash-flow</wp:category_nicename>
  <wp:category_parent/>
  <wp:cat_name><![CDATA[Cash Flow]]></wp:cat_name>
</wp:category>
<wp:category>
  <wp:term_id>3</wp:term_id>
  <wp:category_nicename>profitability</wp:category_nicename>
  <wp:category_parent/>
  <wp:cat_name><![CDATA[Profitability]]></wp:cat_name>
</wp:category>
<wp:category>
  <wp:term_id>1</wp:term_id>
  <wp:category_nicename>uncategorised</wp:category_nicename>
  <wp:category_parent/>
  <wp:cat_name><![CDATA[Uncategorised]]></wp:cat_name>
</wp:category>

<item>
  <title>Article: 7 ways to boost your profit margins</title>
  <link>http://hzhapr15a.dmclub.net/finances/7-ways-to-boost-your-profit-margins/</link>
  <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2015 22:25:23 +0000</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>rwhite</dc:creator>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">http://hzhapr15a.dmclub.net/finances/?p=7</guid>
  <description/>
  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<a href="http://hzhapr15a.dmclub.net/finances/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2015/03/Kelly-Clifford3.jpg"><img class="alignright size-medium wp-image-8" src="http://hzhapr15a.dmclub.net/finances/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2015/03/Kelly-Clifford3-292x300.jpg" alt="Kelly-Clifford" width="292" height="300" /></a>Profit is the aim of the game for most businesses, otherwise what is the point of having to deal with all the curve balls that are frequently thrown at us as business owners? If you are in business purely for the love of what you do, then you can do what you do for enjoyment, perhaps as a hobby. You don’t necessarily need the additional burden of dealing with everything that comes with running a business if that is your desired outcome.<!--more-->

The purpose of a business is to make money. It is how that profit is used that differentiates a private business from a charitable organisation. Both need to make a profit, though. The profits in a private company are generally utilised by the owner for whatever they choose, whereas the profits of a charity are used to re-invest and fund new services. Don’t be mistaken, they must both make money to survive.

So let’s look at 7 things you can do to boost your profit margins:
<h3><strong>Increase your prices </strong></h3>
The key here is to make sure any price increases are greater than any increase in the underlying costs for providing that product or service, so that it has a positive impact on the margins being made. How long has it been since you looked at your prices? When was the last time you raised them?<strong>
</strong>

Obviously, the ability to increase prices will be dependent on the type of business you operate and the marketplace you operate in. A business in a competitive marketplace is less likely to be able to increase prices easily than a business that has differentiated itself from its competition.
<h3><strong>Streamline your operations</strong></h3>
Reduce unnecessary management. Systemise the routine, humanise the exceptions. It’s all about becoming more efficient. Reduce duplication where possible and automate as much as possible. Make sure you are taking advantage of any technological advancements that are relevant for your business that can help you provide your products and services more efficiently, which generally translates into lower costs.
<h3><strong>Know your actual costs</strong></h3>
You can’t improve what you don’t know. Know what things cost and make sure you include everything. Don’t leave any costs out. To better manage the results you need to have access to regular management information on this area, which should be produced frequently. Stay on top of the numbers. Monitor performance regularly, always keeping your profit in focus!
<h3><strong>Pay with cash rather than loan interest</strong></h3>
Interest on loans and overdrafts is a cost to a business so therefore reduces your margins. Don’t pay with debt if you don’t need to, especially if you have cash available to pay instead. It’s not always possible to do this but with careful management of your cash flow, the need for using such costly things as factoring and invoice discounting can usually be eliminated.
<h3><strong>Keep overheads to a minimum </strong></h3>
Don’t take on any unnecessary cost commitments that aren’t linked to revenue generation activities. Stay lean and keep your overheads under control.
<h3><strong>Buy only what you need</strong></h3>
Don’t have excess supplies hanging around unnecessarily. Have a system in place to control the purchases of your team. This could be done by only allowing your team to buy with an authorised purchase order. Any money tied up in unnecessary supplies is money that isn’t working for you to help generate more revenue.
<h3><strong>Reduce all costs by 10%</strong></h3>
Undertake a business-wide campaign to cut all costs by 10%, or whatever percentage reduction you are seeking. Perhaps consider incentivising and rewarding your team for achieving whatever cost reduction target you set.<strong>
</strong>
<h2> About the author</h2>
<strong>Kelly Clifford</strong> is a Profit Specialist, the best-selling author of <em><a href="http://www.profitinfocus.com/profit-rocket-the-five-key-focus-areas-to-skyrocket-your-profit/">Profit Rocket:</a> The 5 Key Focus Areas To Skyrocket Your Profit. </em>He is the creator and founder of the innovative profit improvement platform for small business called <em>Profit Pod,</em> that is <span style="text-decoration: underline;">guaranteed</span> to deliver results as part of his mission to help at least 100,000 small businesses to improve their profit by at least 20% over 12 months by 2020. It’s FREE to get started here: <a href="https://www.profitpod.com">https://www.profitpod.com</a>

&nbsp;]]></content:encoded>
  <excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
  <wp:post_id>7</wp:post_id>
  <wp:post_date>2015-03-25 22:25:23</wp:post_date>
  <wp:post_date_gmt>2015-03-25 22:25:23</wp:post_date_gmt>
  <wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
  <wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
  <wp:post_name>7-ways-to-boost-your-profit-margins</wp:post_name>
  <wp:status>publish</wp:status>
  <wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
  <wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
  <wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
  <wp:post_password/>
  <wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
  <category domain="category" nicename="profitability"><![CDATA[Profitability]]></category>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_bizclub_static_content</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_bizclub_static_title</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_bizclub_top_contributors</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_bizclub_related_pages</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[a:2:{s:3:"csv";s:0:"";s:4:"data";a:1:{i:0;s:0:"";}}]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_bizclub_sub_title</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_bizclub_wpt_settings</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
</item>
<item>
  <title>Kelly-Clifford</title>
  <link>http://hzhapr15a.dmclub.net/finances/7-ways-to-boost-your-profit-margins/kelly-clifford/</link>
  <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2015 22:25:14 +0000</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>rwhite</dc:creator>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">http://hzhapr15a.dmclub.net/finances/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2015/03/Kelly-Clifford3.jpg</guid>
  <description/>
  <content:encoded><![CDATA[]]></content:encoded>
  <excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
  <wp:post_id>8</wp:post_id>
  <wp:post_date>2015-03-25 22:25:14</wp:post_date>
  <wp:post_date_gmt>2015-03-25 22:25:14</wp:post_date_gmt>
  <wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
  <wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
  <wp:post_name>kelly-clifford</wp:post_name>
  <wp:status>inherit</wp:status>
  <wp:post_parent>7</wp:post_parent>
  <wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
  <wp:post_type>attachment</wp:post_type>
  <wp:post_password/>
  <wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
  <wp:attachment_url>http://hzhapr15a.dmclub.net/finances/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2015/03/Kelly-Clifford3.jpg</wp:attachment_url>
</item>
<item>
  <title>Article: Upping the profit ante</title>
  <link>http://hzhapr15a.dmclub.net/finances/upping-the-profit-ante/</link>
  <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2015 22:28:38 +0000</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>rwhite</dc:creator>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">http://hzhapr15a.dmclub.net/finances/?p=11</guid>
  <description/>
  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<a href="http://hzhapr15a.dmclub.net/finances/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2015/03/Kelly-Clifford3.jpg"><img class="alignright size-medium wp-image-8" src="http://hzhapr15a.dmclub.net/finances/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2015/03/Kelly-Clifford3-292x300.jpg" alt="Kelly-Clifford" /></a>If you are like the owners of most small businesses, you are probably more focused on “working in your business” rather than "working on your business".

In business, the bottom line is the bottom line! We need to be taking a step back and checking that we are not leaving profit on the proverbial table.

If you are ready to start making more money from your business, then here are some of the things to bear in mind:
<h3><strong>Numbers aren</strong><strong>’</strong><strong>t to be feared</strong></h3>
Let’s dispel any illusions right now. Numbers aren’t scary, mythical monsters; they can’t hurt you physically but they do have tremendous power when harnessed properly. The numbers side of a business is one of the most important elements of any successful business venture, however, if ignored it is important to recognise and acknowledge that there will be consequences.
<h3><strong>Don</strong><strong>’</strong><strong>t be an ostrich</strong></h3>
The classic reaction by business owners who are reeling off all the excuses they can to justify why they do what they do is to demonstrate an ostrich mentality. They have their head firmly wedged in the sand, ignoring the financial reality of their business. The problem with this approach is that it doesn’t achieve anything. Sure, it may make you feel better in the short term, but it does nothing to improve things. It generally makes the situation worse and could ultimately prove fatal for the business as a whole if left for too long.
<h3><strong>Balance between </strong><strong>‘</strong><strong>Optimism</strong><strong>’</strong><strong> and </strong><strong>‘</strong><strong>Realism </strong><strong>’</strong></h3>
Being negative all the time doesn’t help but neither does being over-optimistic, with your head in the clouds and not seeing the reality of what’s going on in your business. Grounded optimism is the order of the day. It’s about having a glass half full view as opposed to a glass half-empty perspective for whatever obstacles or challenges you face.
<h3><strong>Understand your </strong><strong>‘</strong><strong>bottom-line</strong><strong>’</strong></h3>
By bottom-line I am referring to the main drivers that affect your ability to make a profit. It is imperative that you understand the underlying drivers of your business so you know exactly what to focus your energies on to grow and expand your business in a profitable way.
<h3><strong>Revenue vs <span style="text-decoration: underline;">Profitable Revenue</span></strong></h3>
There is a very important distinction that must be made here. Just because you have decided to charge a certain amount for your products and services is not a guarantee that you are making a profit on that revenue, because you probably haven’t taken the time to actually sit down and work out whether you are making a profit on what you are charging or not. The reality is that just because money is flowing into your bank account from revenue, doesn’t necessarily mean you are making a profit on it.
<h3><strong>A Profit <span style="text-decoration: underline;">that’s banked </span>is King</strong></h3>
It is not the end of the story when you invoice your client. You must ensure that the payment is collected in accordance with your payment terms.  There is no point in invoicing a client if payment is not collected for it. Remember, a profit isn’t actually earned until the amount for the invoice is physically received as cash in your business bank account. Be proactive in the collection of your invoices.
<h2>About the author</h2>
<strong>Kelly Clifford</strong> is a Profit Specialist, the best-selling author of <em><a href="http://www.profitinfocus.com/profit-rocket-the-five-key-focus-areas-to-skyrocket-your-profit/">Profit Rocket:</a> The 5 Key Focus Areas To Skyrocket Your Profit. </em>He is the creator and founder of the innovative profit improvement platform for small business called <em>Profit Pod,</em> that is <span style="text-decoration: underline;">guaranteed</span> to deliver results as part of his mission to help at least 100,000 small businesses to improve their profit by at least 20% over 12 months by 2020. It’s FREE to get started here: <a href="https://www.profitpod.com">https://www.profitpod.com</a>]]></content:encoded>
  <excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
  <wp:post_id>11</wp:post_id>
  <wp:post_date>2015-03-25 22:28:38</wp:post_date>
  <wp:post_date_gmt>2015-03-25 22:28:38</wp:post_date_gmt>
  <wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
  <wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
  <wp:post_name>upping-the-profit-ante</wp:post_name>
  <wp:status>publish</wp:status>
  <wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
  <wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
  <wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
  <wp:post_password/>
  <wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
  <category domain="category" nicename="profitability"><![CDATA[Profitability]]></category>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_bizclub_static_content</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_bizclub_static_title</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_bizclub_top_contributors</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_bizclub_related_pages</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[a:2:{s:3:"csv";s:0:"";s:4:"data";a:1:{i:0;s:0:"";}}]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_bizclub_sub_title</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_bizclub_wpt_settings</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
</item>
<item>
  <title>Article: The three key ingredients for growing your profits</title>
  <link>http://hzhapr15a.dmclub.net/finances/the-three-key-ingredients-for-growing-your-profits/</link>
  <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2015 22:29:56 +0000</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>rwhite</dc:creator>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">http://hzhapr15a.dmclub.net/finances/?p=13</guid>
  <description/>
  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<a href="http://hzhapr15a.dmclub.net/finances/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2015/03/Kelly-Clifford3.jpg"><img class="alignright size-medium wp-image-8" src="http://hzhapr15a.dmclub.net/finances/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2015/03/Kelly-Clifford3-292x300.jpg" alt="Kelly-Clifford" /></a>Let’s be real right from the outset, being in business for yourself isn't always easy. If it were an easy thing to do then everyone would be doing it. As business owners, we find ourselves, particularly in the early stages of a business, having to be a master juggler in that we are managing a whole host of different tasks at seemingly the same time.

Not only are you consumed with the ‘doing part’ of providing your products and services but you find that there is a myriad of other things you need to be concerned with such as marketing, managing staff, being on top of the numbers, staying updated on the ever-changing legislation landscape and ensuring that you are on top of any red-tape burden that is imposed on your business. The list doesn’t end there, but you get the idea.

Being passionate about what you do, or good at what you do, isn't enough to build a successful and profitable business. Anyone can have a good idea, but it takes someone very special to build a successful business. So to avoid becoming part of the nasty statistic that shows that over 80% of businesses ultimately fail in the UK, with a higher mortality rate for start-ups, it is really important that you embark on your journey with a solid foundation in place. The three key ingredients or 3Ps for doing this are:
<h3><strong style="line-height: 1.5;">Passion</strong></h3>
Being passionate about what you do is so important because during the more challenging periods, which you will most certainly face when establishing your new business, it is this passion that will carry you and propel you to overcome whatever obstacles you face. Being passionate about what you do is not enough by itself but is a vital ingredient in any successful business.
<h3><strong style="line-height: 1.5;">Preparation</strong></h3>
Preparation is all about making sure you have a viable business model before you begin. It is about being clear on what your proposition is and who your target market is. A business plan is a vital document that must be prepared. In a nutshell, a business plan is the road map of your business. It shows the destination you are seeking and details the path you will follow and the resources needed for you to get there. Financial projections form a major part of a business plan. You must know your numbers. Remember a business that fails to plan, plans to fail!
<h3><strong style="line-height: 1.5;">Persistence</strong></h3>
Provided you are passionate about what you do, and have done the necessary preparation, then you must have the drive, motivation and determination to see it through and not give up at the first hurdle.

But provided you have all of the three ingredients covered then there is absolutely nothing to fear about going into business for yourself. There will be obstacles and challenges but there is also no greater feeling and sense of achievement than being the master of your own destiny and building your own successful business. Good luck!
<h2>About the author</h2>
<strong>Kelly Clifford</strong> is a Profit Specialist, the best-selling author of <em><a href="http://www.profitinfocus.com/profit-rocket-the-five-key-focus-areas-to-skyrocket-your-profit/">Profit Rocket:</a> The 5 Key Focus Areas To Skyrocket Your Profit. </em>He is the creator and founder of the innovative profit improvement platform for small business called <em>Profit Pod,</em> that is <span style="text-decoration: underline;">guaranteed</span> to deliver results as part of his mission to help at least 100,000 small businesses to improve their profit by at least 20% over 12 months by 2020. It’s FREE to get started here: <a href="https://www.profitpod.com">https://www.profitpod.com</a>]]></content:encoded>
  <excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
  <wp:post_id>13</wp:post_id>
  <wp:post_date>2015-03-25 22:29:56</wp:post_date>
  <wp:post_date_gmt>2015-03-25 22:29:56</wp:post_date_gmt>
  <wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
  <wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
  <wp:post_name>the-three-key-ingredients-for-growing-your-profits</wp:post_name>
  <wp:status>publish</wp:status>
  <wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
  <wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
  <wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
  <wp:post_password/>
  <wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
  <category domain="category" nicename="profitability"><![CDATA[Profitability]]></category>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_bizclub_static_content</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_bizclub_static_title</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_bizclub_top_contributors</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_bizclub_related_pages</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[a:2:{s:3:"csv";s:0:"";s:4:"data";a:1:{i:0;s:0:"";}}]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_bizclub_sub_title</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_bizclub_wpt_settings</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
</item>
<item>
  <title>Finance</title>
  <link>http://hzhapr15a.dmclub.net/finances/</link>
  <pubDate>Tue, 07 Apr 2015 11:14:14 +0000</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>rwhite</dc:creator>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">http://hzhapr15a.dmclub.net/finances/?page_id=18</guid>
  <description/>
  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<a href="http://hzhapr15a.dmclub.net/finances/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2015/04/Finance-small3.jpg"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-20" src="http://hzhapr15a.dmclub.net/finances/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2015/04/Finance-small3.jpg" alt="Finance small" /></a>
<h4>Welcome to the Finance BizClub interest area. Our mission is to help you gain greater control over the finances of your business so that your increase profits and cash flow.</h4>
<h4>Through a combination of articles, seminars, clinics, and masterclasses we will be covering the following subject areas:</h4>
<h2>Profitability</h2>
Providing you with ideas and expert advice so that you can squeeze more profit from your business.
<h2>Cash flow</h2>
Cash flow is the lifeblood of any business and we will help you maximise cash and gain access to funding for business growth.
<h2>Planning and forecasting</h2>
Tips and advice for enabling you to better plan for the future.
<h2>Accounting</h2>
Tips and advice for staying on top of the numbers of your business and using the numbers to boost profits.
<h2>Saving tax</h2>
Tips and advice from tax experts on how to minimise tax and take advantage of tax breaks.]]></content:encoded>
  <excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
  <wp:post_id>18</wp:post_id>
  <wp:post_date>2015-04-07 12:14:14</wp:post_date>
  <wp:post_date_gmt>2015-04-07 11:14:14</wp:post_date_gmt>
  <wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
  <wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
  <wp:post_name>finance</wp:post_name>
  <wp:status>publish</wp:status>
  <wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
  <wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
  <wp:post_type>page</wp:post_type>
  <wp:post_password/>
  <wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_wp_page_template</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_bizclub_static_content</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_bizclub_static_title</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_bizclub_top_contributors</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_bizclub_related_pages</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[a:2:{s:3:"csv";s:0:"";s:4:"data";a:1:{i:0;s:0:"";}}]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_bizclub_sub_title</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_bizclub_wpt_settings</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[2,2,1,2,1,0,2,0,0,1,0]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_bizclub_page_type</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[wel]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
</item>
<item>
  <title>Finance small</title>
  <link>http://hzhapr15a.dmclub.net/finances/finance/finance-small/</link>
  <pubDate>Tue, 07 Apr 2015 11:15:29 +0000</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>rwhite</dc:creator>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">http://hzhapr15a.dmclub.net/finances/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2015/04/Finance-small3.jpg</guid>
  <description/>
  <content:encoded><![CDATA[]]></content:encoded>
  <excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
  <wp:post_id>20</wp:post_id>
  <wp:post_date>2015-04-07 12:15:29</wp:post_date>
  <wp:post_date_gmt>2015-04-07 11:15:29</wp:post_date_gmt>
  <wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
  <wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
  <wp:post_name>finance-small</wp:post_name>
  <wp:status>inherit</wp:status>
  <wp:post_parent>18</wp:post_parent>
  <wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
  <wp:post_type>attachment</wp:post_type>
  <wp:post_password/>
  <wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
  <wp:attachment_url>http://hzhapr15a.dmclub.net/finances/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2015/04/Finance-small3.jpg</wp:attachment_url>
</item>
<item>
  <title>Article: How to get the bank manager to say 'Yes!'</title>
  <link>http://hzhapr15a.dmclub.net/finances/how-to-get-the-bank-manager-to-say-yes/</link>
  <pubDate>Tue, 07 Apr 2015 16:12:29 +0000</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>rwhite</dc:creator>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">http://hzhapr15a.dmclub.net/finances/?p=23</guid>
  <description/>
  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<a href="http://hzhapr15a.dmclub.net/finances/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2015/04/chris-burton-brown4.jpg"><img class="alignright wp-image-27" src="http://hzhapr15a.dmclub.net/finances/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2015/04/chris-burton-brown4-300x300.jpg" alt="chris burton brown" width="250" height="250" /></a>Few things are as exciting as taking your business to the next level. Yet by the same token it can be a pretty daunting affair if reaching that next level means approaching the bank manager for funding.

Whether you’ve already been turned down in the past, or you have your reservations about applying for a business loan, help is at hand. Here are my top tips for getting that resounding ‘Yes’ from your bank manager.
<h3>Be passionate</h3>
More than your products, more than your outstanding sales force, the biggest asset your business possesses is your passion for what you do. This is especially true when it comes to applying for funding. If you can’t demonstrate that you absolutely believe in your business, how can you expect the bank manager to have faith that your idea will work?
<h3>Be articulate</h3>
Having that unbridled passion for your business may be vital, but an enthusiastic pitch to your bank manager is not enough. You need to be able to clearly communicate what you’re looking to achieve.

You’ll need to convince your bank manager that you absolutely know what you’re talking about, and that means articulating your ideas well. Make clear, concise points that demonstrate you’ve really done your homework and have a solid plan.
<h3>Know your numbers</h3>
The goal here is to prove your financial credibility, and to do that, you’re going to need to know your business inside out, especially when it comes to the figures.

Your bank manager is only going to give you the money if they believe they’ll get it back. So they’ll want to see credible numbers before they can be sure your project is an acceptable risk.
<h3>Avoid over-exaggerating</h3>
Avoid making huge claims that you can’t back up with your market research and a solid business plan.

Again, a bank manager will want to see strong evidence that they’ll get their money back, plus interest, before they agree to anything, so it’s important to stick to the facts and avoid the temptation to promise more than you can deliver.
<h3>Know your market</h3>
Having a good understanding of the market you’re getting into is vital in proving that you have a viable business model.

Know your market and the potential for you to succeed in that market. Your bank manager will want to see that you’re experienced in the field or industry, that you understand who your target customers are and what they want from a business like yours.

Really get to know your competitors too, and how you stand out from the pack. Prove that you have a clearly defined USP that ensures your business will be able to cut it when there’s lots of other companies out there all doing a similar thing.
<h3>Consider the risks</h3>
A big part of knowing your market is knowing the risks that come with it. If things go wrong that you haven’t planned for, the banks are unlikely to get their money back, so you’ll have to convince them that you have considered the risks and have contingency plans in place for dealing with the risks.

Give a lot of thought to the potential problems. The last thing you want is for a bank manager to ask about a scenario you hadn’t considered. That’s going to throw you off and give them the idea that you don’t know what you’re doing.

Show them that you’re well-prepared for those problems, and you’ll have a much easier time getting that resounding yes from your bank manager.
<h3>Combine everything into a business plan</h3>
You’ve got the facts in place, you’ve got stacks of market research surveys and plenty of evidence to back up your claim that there’s a market out there for your new product or service, and that you’re the right person to provide it.
Now it’s time to put it all together into a business plan, including the numbers. If your business already has a business plan in place, it will pay to revamp and update it, focussing your efforts on showing that you’ve really thought of everything before approaching the bank manager.
<h2>About the author</h2>
Chris Burton-Brown is the founder of Mylor Financial Management and is a specialist Finance Director, helping SME business owners to manage and grow their businesses from a financial perspective. Chris is a Chartered Accountant with 25 years experience working within companies, during which held 3 Finance Director positions and other senior finance roles. He has experience taking two companies through the sale process, raising proceeds of £40-50m in each case.]]></content:encoded>
  <excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
  <wp:post_id>23</wp:post_id>
  <wp:post_date>2015-04-07 17:12:29</wp:post_date>
  <wp:post_date_gmt>2015-04-07 16:12:29</wp:post_date_gmt>
  <wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
  <wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
  <wp:post_name>how-to-get-the-bank-manager-to-say-yes</wp:post_name>
  <wp:status>publish</wp:status>
  <wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
  <wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
  <wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
  <wp:post_password/>
  <wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
  <category domain="category" nicename="cash-flow"><![CDATA[Cash Flow]]></category>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_bizclub_static_content</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_bizclub_static_title</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_bizclub_top_contributors</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_bizclub_related_pages</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[a:2:{s:3:"csv";s:0:"";s:4:"data";a:1:{i:0;s:0:"";}}]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_bizclub_sub_title</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_bizclub_wpt_settings</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
</item>
<item>
  <title>chris burton brown</title>
  <link>http://hzhapr15a.dmclub.net/finances/how-to-get-the-bank-manager-to-say-yes/chris-burton-brown/</link>
  <pubDate>Tue, 07 Apr 2015 16:09:28 +0000</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>rwhite</dc:creator>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">http://hzhapr15a.dmclub.net/finances/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2015/04/chris-burton-brown4.jpg</guid>
  <description/>
  <content:encoded><![CDATA[]]></content:encoded>
  <excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
  <wp:post_id>27</wp:post_id>
  <wp:post_date>2015-04-07 17:09:28</wp:post_date>
  <wp:post_date_gmt>2015-04-07 16:09:28</wp:post_date_gmt>
  <wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
  <wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
  <wp:post_name>chris-burton-brown</wp:post_name>
  <wp:status>inherit</wp:status>
  <wp:post_parent>23</wp:post_parent>
  <wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
  <wp:post_type>attachment</wp:post_type>
  <wp:post_password/>
  <wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
  <wp:attachment_url>http://hzhapr15a.dmclub.net/finances/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2015/04/chris-burton-brown4.jpg</wp:attachment_url>
</item>
  </channel>
</rss>
